previously.tv 2015-09-06

# Privacy Policy • Previously.TV

It is our policy to respect the privacy of the people who access and use our site and the services we provide to you on the site. Your accessing and continued use of our site and services constitutes your consent to and acceptance of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to information that you provide to us through our site and our services, and when you access, download, purchase or use any information, services, products or content appearing on our site. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this site. You should consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site and/or fill out a form. When registering or filling out a form on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, and age.  However, you may visit our site anonymously, if you prefer.

We, and/or our ad providers, may also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as technical data or information such as your age, gender or interests.  This information will not identify you personally.   Here are examples of such information that may be collected:

Your IP address, which information can be used to deliver our webpages to you on request, to tailor or suit to the interests of our users and to measure traffic within our site.

Cookies, which are small text files that may be used to collect information about your activity on the site.  You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but, if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other users to our site.  Cookies are harmless, but they may contain demographic information and, depending on your browser, these cookies may not normally be deleted when your cookies are otherwise deleted.  Please check your browser to determine where these types of cookies are stored and how they may be deleted.

Web beacons, which are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of the site and to help determine the effectiveness of promotional or advertising campaigns.  When used in html-formatted email messages, web beacons can tell the sender whether and when the email has been opened.  Unlike cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages.

**We and/or our ad providers collect the above non-personally identifiable information from all visitors to our site.   If you do not want us or ad providers to have access to this information, please do not visit our site.**

Also, some ads on this site may be provided through Google. Google uses a cookie system known as DART, which enables Google to provide ads specifically to you, based on your visits to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy and following the instructions there.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

### How do we protect your information?

We offer the use of a secure server. However, we cannot and do not guarantee that, despite our security efforts, your private information cannot be obtained by a third party.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes.  We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Despite the foregoing, please remember that this privacy statement applies solely to information collected on our site.  Our site may contain links to other web sites.  We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of other web sites to which we link or which link to us.  Also, we may use advertisers, third party ad networks, and other advertising companies to serve ads on our site.  Please be advised that such advertising companies may gather information about your visit to our site or other sites (such as through cookies, web beacons and other technologies) to enable such advertising companies to market products or services to you, to monitor which ads have been served to your browser and which webpages you were viewing when such ads were delivered.  **Please note that our policy does not cover the collection and use of information by such third parties**.

If all or part of our assets are acquired by, sold or otherwise transferred to another party, or in the event of a merger, you grant us the right to assign to such other party the personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information collected via the site.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent, except as set forth above.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://previously.tv/terms-of-use/>

### Disclaimer

**YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US.   HOWEVER, NO DATA TRANSMISSIONS OVER THE INTERNET CAN BE GUARANTEED TO BE 100% SECURE.  CONSEQUENTLY, WE CANNOT ENSURE OR WARRANT THE SECURITY OF ANY INFORMATION YOU TRANSMIT TO US.  YOU UNDERSTAND THAT ANY INFORMATION THAT YOU TRANSFER TO US IS DONE AT YOUR OWN RISK.  ONCE WE RECEIVE YOUR TRANSMISSION, WE WILL MAKE REASONABLE EFFORTS TO ENSURE SECURITY ON OUR SYSTEMS.  HOWEVER, THIS IS NOT A GUARANTEE THAT SUCH INFORMATION MAY NOT BE ACCESSED, DISCLOSED, ALTERED OR DESTROYED BY BREACH OF OUR SYSTEMS.  IF WE LEARN OF A SECURITY SYSTEM BREACH WE MAY ATTEMPT TO NOTIFY YOU ELECTRONICALLY SO THAT YOU CAN TAKE APPROPRIATE PROTECTIVE STEPS.  BY USING THE SITE OR PROVIDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO US YOU AGREE THAT WE CAN COMMUNICATE WITH YOU ELECTRONICALLY REGARDING SECURITY, PRIVACY AND ADMINISTRATIVE ISSUES RELATING TO YOUR USE OF THIS SITE.  WE MAY POST A NOTICE ON OUR SITE IF A SECURITY BREACH OCCURS.  WE MAY ALSO SEND AN EMAIL TO YOU AT THE EMAIL ADDRESS YOU HAVE PROVIDED TO US.**

###  Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on April 13, 2013.

###  Consumer Education Related to Social Networking

Creating a safe social networking environment is important to us. While we do not target or knowingly allow users under 13 to use ours site, interested persons may visit the following links created by the Federal Trade Commission to learn more about social networking safety tips:  
<http://onguardonline.gov/socialnetworking_youth.html>

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Brother of Menelaus Inc.  
285 5th Ave., Box 488  
Brooklyn NY 11215  
United States
